{
  "Questions": {
      "Questions set 0": [
        {
          "Question": "___________ hesaru Enu? \n Eng: What is your name?",
          "solution": 1,
          "options": {
            "one": "ninna",
            "two": "nanna",
            "three": "ninage",
            "four": "neenu"
          }
        },
        {
          "Question": "thinDi ___________? \n Eng: Had breakfast?",
          "solution": 2,
          "options": {
            "one": "aaythu",
            "two": "aaytha?",
            "three": "aagilla",
            "four": "aagilwa?"
          }
        },
        {
          "Question": "Question three",
          "solution": 4,
          "options": {
            "one": "value",
            "two": "value",
            "three": "value",
            "four": "value"
          }
        },
        {
          "Question": "Question four",
          "solution": 1,
          "options": {
            "one": "value",
            "two": "value",
            "three": "value",
            "four": "value"
          }
        },
        {
          "Question": "Question five",
          "solution": 1,
          "options": {
            "one": "value",
            "two": "value",
            "three": "value",
            "four": "value"
          }
        }
      ],
    "Questions set 1": [
      {
        "Question": "Eng: What is your name? \n ___________ hesaru Enu? SET 1",
        "solution": 1,
        "options": {
          "one": "ninna",
          "two": "nanna",
          "three": "ninage",
          "four": "neenu"
        }
      },
      {
        "Question": "thinDi ___________? \n Eng: Had breakfast?",
        "solution": 2,
        "options": {
          "one": "aaythu",
          "two": "aaytha?",
          "three": "aagilla",
          "four": "aagilwa?"
        }
      },
      {
        "Question": "Question three",
        "solution": 4,
        "options": {
          "one": "value",
          "two": "value",
          "three": "value",
          "four": "value"
        }
      },
      {
        "Question": "Question four",
        "solution": 1,
        "options": {
          "one": "value",
          "two": "value",
          "three": "value",
          "four": "value"
        }
      },
      {
        "Question": "Question five",
        "solution": 1,
        "options": {
          "one": "value",
          "two": "value",
          "three": "value",
          "four": "value"
        }
      }
    ],
    "Questions set 2": [
      {
        "Question": "Eng: What is your name? \n ___________ hesaru Enu? SET 2",
        "solution": 1,
        "options": {
          "one": "ninna",
          "two": "nanna",
          "three": "ninage",
          "four": "neenu"
        }
      },
      {
        "Question": "thinDi ___________? \n Eng: Had breakfast?",
        "solution": 2,
        "options": {
          "one": "aaythu",
          "two": "aaytha?",
          "three": "aagilla",
          "four": "aagilwa?"
        }
      },
      {
        "Question": "Question three",
        "solution": 4,
        "options": {
          "one": "value",
          "two": "value",
          "three": "value",
          "four": "value"
        }
      },
      {
        "Question": "Question four",
        "solution": 1,
        "options": {
          "one": "value",
          "two": "value",
          "three": "value",
          "four": "value"
        }
      },
      {
        "Question": "Question five",
        "solution": 1,
        "options": {
          "one": "value",
          "two": "value",
          "three": "value",
          "four": "value"
        }
      }
    ]
    }
}